<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Writing Samples on My Portfolio</title>
    <link>http://example.org/writing_samples/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Writing Samples on My Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/writing_samples/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Compatibility Guide</title>
      <link>http://example.org/writing_samples/compatibility_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/writing_samples/compatibility_guide/</guid>
      <description>Helping Customers Help Themselves Download the Isilon Supportability and Compatability Guide (PDF).
 Overview I was lucky to be asked to create Isilon’s first customer-facing compatibility guide. You might not believe me, but there was no single, authoritative source for compatibility information before.
When customers wanted to upgrade OneFS or buy new Isilon hardware, they had to call Isilon Support or their account manager with compatibility-related questions. This put an unreasonable burden on customers looking for information, who just wanted to look up an answer and get back to work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic Research</title>
      <link>http://example.org/writing_samples/academic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/writing_samples/academic/</guid>
      <description>Ethnographic Field Research: Transit System Overview When I was a graduate student at the University of Washington, I assisted in an ethnographic research study. For one semester, my teammates and I looked at how transit-dependent populations use the King County Metro Transit system, and how vulnerable communities, especially the homeless, overcome barriers to ridership. We identified several systemic issues and proposed human-centered design solutions to make the transit system more fair and inclusive.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>