<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Travis A. Martin&#39;s Portfolio on My Portfolio</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Travis A. Martin&#39;s Portfolio on My Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 12:00:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Personas</title>
      <link>http://example.org/content_strategy/personas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 09:24:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/content_strategy/personas/</guid>
      <description>Download the personas I created (PDF).
 Overview Two UX colleagues and I were asked to create user personas for Isilon. These personas would be used as tools to help align business requirements with customer wants and needs.
A persona is a fictional character that represents a customer or target audience. A persona has a name, a picture, some demographic information, and other meaningful characteristics. Personas are based on user research—in this case, the Isilon personas are based on customer interviews, site visits, and surveys—and are composites of real people from the group the persona represents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heuristic Checklist</title>
      <link>http://example.org/content_strategy/heuristic_checklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 09:45:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/content_strategy/heuristic_checklist/</guid>
      <description>Download my heuristic checklist (PDF).
 Overview I created the following heuristic checklist, based on Nielsen’s heuristics, for the Isilon OneFS web administration interface. Heuristic evaluations are one of the most popular inspection-based methods for identifying usability problems in the user interface. An evaluator systematically examines the interface and compares it against a checklist of usability principles.
This heuristic checklist is used by developers, UX researchers, and writers. It provides a quick and inexpensive way to obtain early feedback in the design process while suggesting corrective measures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Resume</title>
      <link>http://example.org/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 12:01:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/resume/</guid>
      <description>Download the PDF version of my resume.
 I wear many hats: I am a senior technical content developer, content strategist, and UX researcher. I enjoy wrangling complex problems and answering the question “Why?” with qualitative and quantitative data.
 Specialties: content development, content strategy, information design, user research, user-centered design
Skills: DITA; XMetaL; quantitative and qualitative research: field study, focus group, cognitive walkthrough, interview, survey, content audit, heuristic evaluation, card sort, A/B test, wireframes, prototypes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compatibility Guide</title>
      <link>http://example.org/writing_samples/compatibility_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/writing_samples/compatibility_guide/</guid>
      <description>Helping Customers Help Themselves Download the Isilon Supportability and Compatability Guide (PDF).
 Overview I was lucky to be asked to create Isilon’s first customer-facing compatibility guide. You might not believe me, but there was no single, authoritative source for compatibility information before.
When customers wanted to upgrade OneFS or buy new Isilon hardware, they had to call Isilon Support or their account manager with compatibility-related questions. This put an unreasonable burden on customers looking for information, who just wanted to look up an answer and get back to work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic Research</title>
      <link>http://example.org/writing_samples/academic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/writing_samples/academic/</guid>
      <description>Ethnographic Field Research: Transit System Overview When I was a graduate student at the University of Washington, I assisted in an ethnographic research study. For one semester, my teammates and I looked at how transit-dependent populations use the King County Metro Transit system, and how vulnerable communities, especially the homeless, overcome barriers to ridership. We identified several systemic issues and proposed human-centered design solutions to make the transit system more fair and inclusive.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>