<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Content Strategy on My Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://travisamartin.github.io/content_strategy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Content Strategy on My Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 15:33:02 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://travisamartin.github.io/content_strategy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Personas</title>
      <link>https://travisamartin.github.io/content_strategy/personas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 09:24:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://travisamartin.github.io/content_strategy/personas/</guid>
      <description>Download the personas I created (PDF).
 Overview Two UX colleagues and I were asked to create user personas for Isilon. These personas would be used as tools to help align business requirements with customer wants and needs.
A persona is a fictional character that represents a customer or target audience. A persona has a name, a picture, some demographic information, and other meaningful characteristics. Personas are based on user research—in this case, the Isilon personas are based on customer interviews, site visits, and surveys—and are composites of real people from the group the persona represents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Persona Training</title>
      <link>https://travisamartin.github.io/content_strategy/persona_training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 14:52:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://travisamartin.github.io/content_strategy/persona_training/</guid>
      <description>Download the presentation I gave that shows how my team used personas and user stories to improve the OneFS upgrade documentation. (PPT)
 Overivew The Isilon user personas have been used as content strategy and design tools, steering conversations in creative and productive ways. Feature teams refer to Josefina as a tangible user and consider her wants and needs when deciding courses of action to take. As a result, features and entire products have a user-centered quality now that they didn&amp;rsquo;t have before, and customer feedback has been positive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mapping the User Journey</title>
      <link>https://travisamartin.github.io/content_strategy/user_journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 15:33:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://travisamartin.github.io/content_strategy/user_journey/</guid>
      <description>View the customer&amp;rsquo;s OneFS upgrade journey
 Overview I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about making sure that the upgrade experience for Isilon customers goes as smoothly as possible. One of the obstacles that customers face when upgrading OneFS is finding and reading all the upgrade documentation. There are over 400 pages of upgrade-related material, published across 10 documents, that are considered &amp;ldquo;required reading.&amp;rdquo; That&amp;rsquo;s too much. I heard from customers that they don&amp;rsquo;t want to search for information or read long guides to complete an upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heuristic Checklist</title>
      <link>https://travisamartin.github.io/content_strategy/heuristic_checklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 09:45:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://travisamartin.github.io/content_strategy/heuristic_checklist/</guid>
      <description>Download my heuristic checklist (PDF).
 Overview I created the following heuristic checklist, based on Nielsen’s heuristics, for the Isilon OneFS web administration interface. Heuristic evaluations are one of the most popular inspection-based methods for identifying usability problems in the user interface. An evaluator systematically examines the interface and compares it against a checklist of usability principles.
This heuristic checklist is used by developers, UX researchers, and writers. It provides a quick and inexpensive way to obtain early feedback in the design process while suggesting corrective measures.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>